<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.audio.radiochomik" name="RadioChomik" version="1.4.0" provider-name="Alex, Jarek">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
    <provides>audio</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
	<news>
	[fix] Modification for Python3
	[fix] Fixing xbmcvfs bug
	[new] Added polish translation
	</news>
	<assets>
		<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
		<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
	</assets>
    <platform>all</platform>
	<license>GNU General Public License, Version 3</license>
    <website>https://github.com/JaroslawHryszko/RadioChomik/</website>
    <source>https://github.com/JaroslawHryszko/RadioChomik/</source>
    <email>jarek@hryszko.pl</email>
	<reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
    <summary lang="en_GB">RadioChomik is a plugin for listing and listening Internet radios from www.radio-browser.info</summary>
	<summary lang="pl_PL">RadioChomik to wtyczka do wyświetlania i słuchania radia internetowego ze strony www.radio-browser.info</summary>
    <summary lang="bg_BG">RadioChomik е плъгин за изброяване и слушане на интернет радиа от www.radio-browser.info</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">RadioChomik ist ein Plugin zum Auflisten und Anhören von Internet-Radios von www.radio-browser.info</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Plugin for displaying (and listening in a result) Internet radio stations gathered by www.radio-browser.info website. It is a Python3 oriented development of kodi-radio-browser plugin.</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Wtyczka do wyświetlania (i w rezutacie do słuchania) internetowych stacji radiowych gromadzonych przez serwis www.radio-browser.info. Wtyczka powstała specjalnie dla Arniki, aby mogła słuchać ulubionych audycji radiowych.</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">Plugin zur Anzeige (und zum Anhören) von Internet-Radiosendern, die von der Website www.radio-browser.info gesammelt wurden. Es ist eine Python3-orientierte Entwicklung des Kodi-Radio-Browser-Plugins.</description>
	<description lang="bg_BG">Плъгин за показване (и слушане в резултат на това) на интернет радиостанции, събрани от уебсайта www.radio-browser.info. Това е Python3 ориентирана разработка на плъгина kodi-radio-browser.</description>
  </extension>
</addon>
